Guide to the Elmer Holmes Bobst Collection MSS.067
Fales Library and Special Collections
Elmer Holmes Bobst Collection
1862-1978
Fales Library and Special Collections
Bobst, Elmer Holmes
MSS.067
40 Linear Feet
47 sound discs (lacquer) 47 phonograph records: 33-1/3 (16), 78 (31)
2 videocassettes (u-matic)
2 videocassettes (vhs)
40 Reels 40 open reel films
10 Reels 10 open reel audiotapes
15 audiocassettes
Elmer Holmes Bobst was born in 1884 in Clear Springs, Maryland with aspirations to become a doctor, but instead, he taught himself pharmacology. Bobst became manager and treasurer of the Hoffman-LaRoche Chemical Works by 1920. In 1928, Hoffman-LaRoche became Roche-Nutley, and when Bobst retired from there in 1944, he was one of the nation's highest paid corporate executives. In 1945 he took charge of the ailing William Warner Company (later Warner-Lambert) and he remained board chairman. Bobst had close connections to President Eisenhower, but was also a close friend of President Nixon, helped guide his career and contributed generously to his campaigns. In 1968, Bobst became a White House advisor on health issues. Philanthropic pursuits were also of tremendous importance, particularly cancer research and education. The collection includes family documents from the American Civil War, Bobst's documents and artifacts of both a public and private nature.
Conditions Governing Access
Repository permission is required for access. Please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, 212-998-2596, fales.library@nyu.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Elmer Holmes Bobst Collection, donated to New York University by Mrs. Mamdouha Bobst, represents a portion of the records and personal effects of her late husband, Elmer Holmes Bobst. This material was transferred to the New York University Archives by Mrs. Bobst from her residence in New York in 1988 in order to establish a permanent home for the collection in the library which bears the Bobst name. Additional material given by Mrs. Bobst after 1989 has been incorporated with the original gift. The accession number associated with this gift is 1998.067.
Arrangement
Folders are generally arranged alphabetically in seven series:
I: Photograph Albums, Scrapbooks, and Ships' Logs
II: Loose Framed and Unframed Photographs and Prints
III: Awards, Plaques, Medals, Certificates and Honors
IV: Articles, Press Releases, Speeches and Correspondence
V: Film, Audio and Video Tape, Slides and Recordings
VI: Miscellaneous Items and Oversize
VII: Books and Periodicals Belonging to Elmer Holmes Bobst
Biographical Note
Elmer Holmes Bobst lived out the American dream. For this self-educated son of a Lutheran minister, intellect plus hard work did indeed produce great success.
Bobst's father served in the Union army in the Civil War and was a member of the 128th Pennsylvania Infantry. His regiment saw action at Antietam and Chancellorsville where he was captured and paroled. He re-enlisted into the 1st Pennsylvania Cavalry and served until captured and sent to Andersonville in 1864. Isaac Bobst's Civil War experiences are chronicled in Daniel Biles': 'A Soldier's Journey: An Account of Private Isaac Bobst, 128th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry and 1st Pennsylvania Cavalry, from Antietam to Andersonville. Gettysburg, PA: Thomas Publications, 1990 available to view in the Fales Library.
The third of Isaac and Alice (Holmes) Bobst's five children, Elmer (born in 1884) hoped to become a doctor. But he was able to complete just one year at Franklin and Marshall College (on a baseball scholarship) before family financial problems forced him to seek work.
Bobst took a job in a Philadelphia drug store. During his few off hours, he taught himself pharmacology, passing both Pennsylvania's assistant pharmacist and managing registered pharmacist examinations in 1905. Self-study also prepared him to pass the state's preliminary bar examination in 1907. But family responsibilities prevented him from continuing his legal education. The law's loss proved to be commerce's gain, for Bobst went on to help shape the modern pharmaceutical industry and to build two of the industry's greatest firms.
Starting as a salesman at the New York office of the Swiss company Hoffmann-LaRoche in 1911, Bobst became manager and treasurer of the Hoffman-LaRoche Chemical Works by 1920. In 1928, he moved operations to Nutley, New Jersey and restructured the U.S. branch as an independent subsidiary, Roche-Nutley. By 1940, Roche-Nutley was generating two-thirds of Hoffman-LaRoche's total profits, and Bobst, when he retired in 1944, was one of the nation's highest paid corporate executives.(1)
The parent company was not the only beneficiary of Roche-Nutley's success; so were employees of the U.S. subsidiary. As Bobst wrote in his autobiography, "I was so regularly underpaid and overworked... that... when I reached a position where I could do something about decent working conditions and generous employee benefits in the pharmaceutical industry, I did."(2)
Bobst's retirement lasted less than a year. In 1945 he took charge of the ailing William Warner Company. As president and chief executive officer, he turned the company around, later merged it with the Lambert Company, and made it one of the world's largest pharmaceutical manufacturers. He remained board chairman of Warner-Lambert.
Active in politics, Bobst was a close friend of Richard Nixon, helped guide his career, contributed generously to his campaigns, and was instrumental in his joining the New York law firm of Nixon, Mudge, Rose, and Alexander. After Nixon's election in 1968, Bobst became a White House advisor on health issues. But he makes clear in his autobiography his opposition to U.S. military action in Vietnam(3) and his disapproval of the Watergate cover-up.(4)
A man of strong principles, Bobst enjoyed a reputation for fairness and honesty. Columnist Jack Anderson described him as "a veritable saint among the robber barons of the drug industry," who "steered clear of price-fixing and other scandals that have characterized the industry." While with Hoffman-LaRoche, he forced the parent company to end its dealings in illicit drugs. As head of Warner-Lambert he turned down an opportunity to acquire the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, feeling that such an acquisition was inconsistent with his efforts to promote health.(5)
A dedicated philanthropist, he enjoyed great success selling war bonds during World War II. But his major and most sustained commitment was to the American Cancer Society. "As I look over all I have done in my life," Bobst said," there is nothing more rewarding than my Cancer Society experience. If I have performed a service to mankind, that is it."(6) In addition to generous support of the Cancer Society, Bobst also made substantial gifts to such educational institutions as Columbia University, the University of Pennsylvania, Franklin and Marshall College, the Elmer Holmes Bobst Institute of Clinical Research at Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital in Philadelphia, and Chungang University in Seoul, Korea.
A notable contribution to education was his $11.5 million gift to New York University for the Elmer Holmes Bobst Library and Study Center. NYU President James Hester wrote, in his forward to Bobst's autobiography, "Mr. Bobst has made a major contribution to a library because he knows the value of libraries in his own self-education."(7)
Among the many awards accorded Elmer Bobst were honorary degrees from Franklin and Marshall College, Hahnemann Medical College, Rider College, and the University of Pennsylvania. He received the Henry Busby Award from Columbia University's College of Pharmacy in 1961, the National Cancer Society Award in 1962, the Horatio Alger Award in 1965, and the Albert Gallatin Award of New York University in 1966.
Bobst's first wife, the former Ethel Rose, died in 1953. His only child, Elmer Walton Bobst, died in 1964, leaving two daughters and four grandchildren. In 1961, Elmer
Bobst married the former Mamdouha As-Sayyid, a social scientist serving on Lebanon's delegation to the United Nations.
Until his death in 1978, at the age of 93, Bobst remained active. His legacy is a rich one, and his work goes on, sustained today by the philanthropic efforts of his widow, Mamdouha Bobst.
Sources:
(1.) Moritz, Charles. Current Biography Yearbook. New York: Wilson, 1973. p.49.
(2.) Bobst, Elmer Holmes. Bobst: the Autobiography of a Pharmaceutical Pioneer.New York, 1973. p.149.
(3.) Bobst, p.149.
(4.) Moritz, p.50.
(5.) Moritz, p.50.
(6.) Moritz, p.50.
(7.) Moritz, p.50.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the Fales Library with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The contents of this collection represent a portion of the material generated by, or related to, the public and private life of Elmer Holmes Bobst covering the time period between 1863 and 1978. Material covering the period from 1978 to the present time, representing his legacy to New York University and to the world, enriches the collection.
The records have been divided into seven series according to type of artifact or document. Arrangement within series is alphabetical or chronological, except when the physical shape of an item rendered this impractical. Included in the collection are: photograph albums, scrapbooks, loose photographs and prints, awards, medals, plaques, certificates, honors, press releases, newspaper and magazine articles, speeches, correspondence, 16 and 8 millimeter film, audio and video tape, slides, recordings, and memorabilia.
The items in the collection are housed in acid-free boxes of varying size depending on the article in question. A few oversize items are shelved out of series sequence and are so indicated in the series list.
Items of special interest include: The writings of Elmer Holmes Bobst [Series IV, Box 2] Correspondence between Elmer Holmes Bobst and presidents Nixon and Eisenhower [Series IV, Box 8] A number of letters written by Isaac Bobst, the father of Elmer Holmes Bobst during the American Civil War. There is also a spoon that the elder Bobst used while at Andersonville [Series IV, Box 9]. Voice recordings of Elmer Holmes Bobst [Series V, Box 6] include an interview conducted by noted journalist Edward R. Murrow. Several works on pharmaceutical and medical theory from the eighteenth, nineteenth, and twentieth century are included in Series VII.
Separated Materials
The framed oil painting of people working in Renaissance apothecary (MSS.067.cuid20338); and framed oil painting of man working at fire (MSS.067.cuid20339); were removed from the collection and transferred to the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center in February 2019.
Writings (document genre); Sound recordings.; Correspondence.; Voluntary health agencies.; Education -- Societies, etc.; Campaign funds.; Cancer -- Prevention; Personal papers.; Family papers.; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Personal narratives; Pharmaceutical industry.; Artifacts.; Personal correspondence.; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1968; Elections -- United States.; Pharmacy -- Study and teaching.; Philanthropists.; American Cancer Society; Bobst family; Bobst, Ethel Rose; Bobst, Isaac Walton, 1847-1924; Bobst, Mamdouha As-Sayyid; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969; Elmer Holmes Bobst Library; Fuchs, Alfred T.; Hoffmann-LaRoche Chemical Works; La Roche-Nutley (Firm); Murrow, Edward R.; William Warner Company; Warner-Lambert Company; Paul, King of the Hellenes, I, 1901-1964; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Andersonville Prison
- Series I: Photograph Albums, Scrapbooks, and Ships' Logs.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I contains scrapbooks, photographs, correspondence, ships' logs, and other materials that document Bobst's career, travel, professional and personal friendships, and lifelong enthusiasm for yachting.
  - Scrapbook of Elmer Holmes Bobst's early career. Includes early letters of recommendation; correspondence with Hoffman-LaRoche; letters from Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Hellen Keller, Gov. Thomas E. Dewey, Adolph Menjou, and Ramon Navarro, and event group photos., 1903-1940 (Box 1)
  - Photograph album. Contains various portraits of Elmer Holmes Bobst throughout his life; includes a Bobst family portrait, ca. 1900, and a photograph of the "Highwall" estate in Montclair, N.J., 1900-1960 (Box 2)
  - Album of Elmer Holmes Bobst's 25th anniversary with Roche, Inc., 1936-10-15 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook of editorials by Elmer Holmes Bobst, 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook of letters to Hoffman-LaRoche stockholders written by Elmer Holmes Bobst, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Guest Register and Log Book from the Yachts "Alisa III" and "Alisa IV", 1949-1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photograph album of "Alisa III", 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photograph album of the dedication of the new cafeteria, William Warner and Co., 1950 (Box 6)
  - Scrapbook with photographs: "Alisa III Sails the Hills", by Helmuth Klessewetter, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Photograph album of "Cirrhosis Club" fishing cruise aboard the "Alisa IV". Annotated, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Sketchy Record of Our 1951 Peregrinations Aboard Alisa IV. Account of the cruise by Elmer Holmes Bobst. See also Series VI, Oversize Item 6 for a chart of this cruise. (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook with annotated photographs: "All the Way to Mo-Bay on Alisa IV," by Helmuth Klessewetter, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook with annotated photographs: "No Virgins in 1952," by Helmuth Klesswetter. Alissa IV cruise (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photograph album, annotated: New Jersey Savings Bond meeting, Spring Lake, N.J., 1952-08 (Box 7)
  - Scrapbook: Newspapers clippings, speeches, photographs. Includes letters from Dwight D. Eisenhower and Grover Whalen, 1951-1953 (Box 8)
  - Trip to Germany. Scrapbook with newspaper clippings and photographs, multiple copies, 1953-10 (Box 4, Folder 5-10)
  - Album of photographs and sketches for the administration building. 2 vol. Warner-Lambert, Morris Plains, N.J., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Outstanding Events in the History of Roche, Inc., Nutley, N.J., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photograph album. Includes photographs of Elmer Holmes Bobst with Billy Graham, President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower, and signed photographs of Richard Nixon, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook with annotated photographs. Trip to Mimmingen, Germany, 1956-05-25 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Guestbook with signatures of attendees and congratulatory telegrams upon receiving the Cleveland Award, American Cancer Society, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Guest Register of the "Alisa IV", 1953-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photograph album. Cruise of the "Alisa V", 1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photograph album. Cruise of the "Alisa V" to Venezuela. Includes newspaper clippings in English and Spanish., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Guest register of the "Alisa IV" and "Alisa V" including signatures of Richard Nixon, Robert Sarnoff, and Herbert P. Patterson, 1956-1961 (Box 9)
  - Scrapbook with photographs. Annual meeting of the New Jersey Savings Bond Committee, Spring Lake, N.J. Contains photographs of Vice-President Richard Nixon and extensive newspaper clippings regarding his intention to run for the presidency in 1960., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photograph album. Lambert-Hudnut, Lititz, PA, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Visit to Eastleigh, Hampshire, England, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Photograph album, annotated, of Mr. and Mrs. Elmer Holmes Bobst's visit to Germany, 1962-10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Photograph album. Presentation to Elmer Holmes Bobst of the Gallatin Award, New York University, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Visit to Eastleigh, Hampshire, England, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook with photographs and newspaper clippings. Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Institute of Clinical Research, Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital, Philadelphia, PA, 1967-05-31 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Trip to Germany, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Tribute to Elmer Holmes Bobst by the University of Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Yacht Log and Register of the Yacht "Dodo", 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Address Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Carolyn Jackson Address Book for Walter-Lambert Pharmaceutical Co., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ship's Log, Alisa V, 1951-1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Elmer Holmes Bobst, 1936-1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Business Address Book, includes some personal addresses, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Richard M. Nixon Presidential Library commemorative album, 1968-08-08 (Box 106)
- Series II: Loose Framed and Unframed Photographs and Prints.
  Scope and Contents note
  Series II contains photographs of Elmer and Mamdouha Bobst, as well as photographs of others given and inscribed to Bobst. Also in this series are photographs of Bobst yachts.
  See also: Series VI. Oversize Items 1 through 4.
  - Loose photographs including: portraits of Elmer Holmes Bobst, ca.1915-1960; dedication of new Hoffman-LaRoche building, 1938; American Cancer Society Meeting with President Eisenhower, 1953; Cardiology Award Banquet, 1969; photographs of Elmer Holmes Bobst's 85th birthday at the White House with the Nixons., 1938-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Loose photographs of the dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University., undated (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
  - Loose photographs, including informal pictures with political dignitaries: President Richard Nixon, Governor Alfred Driscoll, and others., undated (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs: President Richard Nixon: Inauguration picture, signed; color portrait, signed., undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Framed early Richard Nixon portrait, signed, undated; MSS.067.cuid20389 (Box 86)
  - Presidential portraits in facsimile: Christmas greetings from President Richard Nixon: 1969, George Washington; 1970, Thomas Jefferson; 1972, Theodore Roosevelt; 1973, James Monroe., 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Framed Christmas greetings from President Richard Nixon, Presidential portrait in facsimile, Abraham Lincoln, 1971; MSS.067.cuid20390 (Box 87)
  - Reproduction of Dwight D. Eisenhower portrait by Norman Rockwell, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Framed photographic portrait of Morris Fishbein, 1959-07-22; MSS.067.cuid20391 (Box 85)
  - Framed photographic portrait of John W. Snyder, undated; MSS.067.cuid20392 (Box 85)
  - Portraits of Elmer Holmes Bobst [3]; Elmer Holmes and Mamdouha Bobst., 1920, undated (Box 15, Folder 4-9)
  - Yacht Photograph, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Framed photograph of the Hoffman-LaRoche Building, undated; MSS.067.cuid20387 (Box 88)
  - Photograph of Elmer Holmes Bobst residence, Spring Lake, N.J., mounted on wood plaque, undated; MSS.067.cuid20393 (Box 88)
  - Framed signed portrait of John Cardinal Krol, undated; MSS.067.cuid20388 (Box 90)
  - Framed signed portrait of Terence Cardinal Cooke, undated; MSS.067.cuid20394 (Box 90)
  - Framed signed portrait of Francis Cardinal Spellman, undated; MSS.067.cuid20395 (Box 91)
  - Loose photographs of yachts captained by Elmer Holmes Bobst., undated (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Photographs, personal and professional, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Series III: Awards, Plaques, Medals, Certificates and Honors.
  Series III contains awards, plaques, certificates and other physical artifacts presented to Bobst throughout his life to recognize his professional and philanthropic contributions.
  - Subseries A: Boxed Awards.
    - American-Hungarian Foundation, Theodore Von Karman Award Medal, 1975., MSS.067.cuid20245 (Box 17)
    - Cleveland-Blaine Medal, Election of 1884. From Lois and Tom Evans., undated; MSS.067.cuid20246 (Box 17)
    - Key Man 10 Year Medal. Plaque. [Key missing], undated; MSS.067.cuid20247 (Box 17)
    - United Commercial Travelers, 50 year Member. Plaque, 1969; MSS.067.cuid20248 (Box 17)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower "Atoms for Peace" Medal, 1957; MSS.067.cuid20249 (Box 17)
    - John F. Kennedy Medal, 1963; MSS.067.cuid20250 (Box 17)
    - Richard M. Nixon Campaign Medal, 1960; MSS.067.cuid20251 (Box 17)
    - Bird Watchers Medal, from Richard Nixon, 1966; MSS.067.cuid20252 (Box 17)
    - Richard M. Nixon Medal, 1968; MSS.067.cuid20253 (Box 26)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral Coin, undated; MSS.067.cuid20254 (Box 17)
    - Pope Paul VI Medal, 1963; MSS.067.cuid20255 (Box 17)
    - Pope John Paul II Medal, 1978; MSS.067.cuid20256 (Box 17)
    - National Safety Council Medal, 1963; MSS.067.cuid20257 (Box 18)
    - American Cancer Society Medal, 1962; MSS.067.cuid20258 (Box 18)
    - American Journal of Nursing Influence Medal, undated; MSS.067.cuid20259 (Box 18)
    - New York City Cancer Committee, Clement Cleveland Award, 1956; MSS.067.cuid20260 (Box 18)
    - Gallatin Associates, Life Member Medal, undated; MSS.067.cuid20262 (Box 18, Box 71)
    - Albert Gallatin Award, 1966; MSS.067.cuid20263 (Box 18, Box 71)
    - New York State Citizens Committee for Public Schools. Citation. Paperweight., undated; MSS.067.cuid20264 (Box 18)
    - Franklin and Marshall College, Franklin Club Diplomat. Paperweight., undated; MSS.067.cuid20265 (Box 18)
    - New York State Governor's Club. Paperweight. Signed by Nelson Rockefeller, undated; MSS.067.cuid20266 (Box 18)
    - United States Savings Bond Program, Volunteer Leadership Medal., undated; MSS.067.cuid20267 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Secretary of the Treasury Medal. George Humphrey (2), undated; MSS.067.cuid20268 (Box 18)
    - U.S. Secretary of the Treasury Medal. Robert Anderson., undated; MSS.067.cuid20269 (Box 18)
    - American Cancer Society, Pennsylvania Division. Plaque, 1955; MSS.067.cuid20270 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - U.S Treasury Award of Merit, 1974; MSS.067.cuid20271 (Box 18)
    - U.S. Treasury Award. Proclamation of Elmer Holmes Bobst as Chairman Emeritus, 1974; MSS.067.cuid20272 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Albert Gallatin Award Certificate, 1966; MSS.067.cuid20273 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Salvation Army Association of the Palm Beaches Award for Distinguished Service, 1966; MSS.067.cuid20274 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Franklin and Marshall College, Ford Foundation Leadership Award., undated; MSS.067.cuid20275 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - New Jersey Savings Bond Committee. Six presidential coins [Presidents Roosevelt to Nixon] "in appreciation of patriotic service as Chairman.", undated; MSS.067.cuid20276 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Program. 3 Commemorative Medals "for patriotic contribution. "Spring Lake, N.J., 1959; MSS.067.cuid20277 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Army Emergency Relief Fund, World War II., undated; MSS.067.cuid20278 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Treasury Award. New Jersey Savings Bond, 1953; MSS.067.cuid20279 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Pan American Medical Association, Ambassador of Good Will. Plaque, 1962; MSS.067.cuid20280 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - American Cancer Society. Honorary Member of Board of Directors, 1957; MSS.067.cuid20281 (Box 24)
    - Warner-Chilcott Workers, Havana, Cuba. Certificate of Appreciation., undated; MSS.067.cuid20282 (Box 24)
    - Lititz, Pa. Bi-Centennial Certificate, 1959; MSS.067.cuid20283 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Gallatin Medal, New York University. Presentation Program. [3 copies], 1966; MSS.067.cuid20284 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Franklin and Marshall College. 85th Birthday Salute, 1969; MSS.067.cuid20285 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Franklin and Marshall Varsity Club. Honorary Membership, 1969; MSS.067.cuid20286 (Box 25, Folder 4)